http://www.motorcyclelighting.com/privacy-policy/

Our Commitment to Privacy and Security
Protecting your privacy and security is of the utmost importance to us. To show our commitment to maintaining your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. We encourage you to ask questions and to be cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.
Essential Information We Collect
In operating our store, it is essential for us to capture some information about your device, such as
your IP address and information related to your visit when you browse our store. For example, this
might include timestamps, the last page or product you visited, the indication that you logged in and more.
We do that in order to:
Remember who you are after you login so that you do not need to authenticate at each
click.
Monitor if our website is running with the high performance we are dedicated to
providing.
Let you browse between products without having to start back from the home page at
each click.
Remember if you put something in your shopping cart before you decide to checkout.
Control that your data is processed securely.
We call the information mentioned above “essential information” and we collect it through the
use of cookies. Cookies are small text files that most websites uses. A website places cookies in the
web browser and then reads the information collected through the cookies every time the user
performs an action. We use cookies. Without enabling this mechanism and this kind of cookies
(first party cookies), we could not provide you with the smooth experience that you expect while
you are navigating.
Order Information
If you buy something from our store, we will need more specific information about you. To fully
process your order and ship the merchandise you selected, we need your personal data such as
your first and last name, your email address and your shipping and billing address. We also use
your contact and order information to send you communications related to the processing of your
order. We will ask you to provide this information in our “checkout page” before letting you
finalize your purchase with the payment. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order, and it is our right to refuse any order for any reason we determine to be valid.
Accounts
You can sign up for an account if you’d like. We will remember your information
and, when you decide to buy our products, you do not have to provide all of your information over
again -- you just have to login. Before registering your account, we will ask you to expressly
provide your consent to this privacy policy. Only if you give us your consent, we will open your
account. We also give you the possibility to easily withdraw your consent and delete your account. Just
connect with us at the contact details at the bottom of the page.
Partial Purchases
If you have started to buy one of our products, but have not completed the purchase, you may
have provided partial information, such as your email. In that case, we might send you an email to
remind you about your interest. If you are not comfortable in receiving further emails of this kind,
we will give you a simple opportunity to opt-out. Your privacy means a lot to us and we will stop
sending you these communications right away.
Reviews
If you have completed a purchase, we will send you an email to ask you to review the product you
bought. We want to be sure that whether you love your purchase or have a complaint, you can
share your opinion with other customers. You may also be prompted when you complete your order to receive a survey from Google about your shopping experience.
Personalization
We also use some specific information related to your visit, such as the timestamp of your visit, the
page or the product you viewed, where you are coming from (if you came to our store because you
clicked on an advertisement or you just opened our direct link). This is very similar to the
“essential information,” but we use it to provide you with a personalized experience. The
information on your visit provides us with insights on your interests and allows us to send you
relevant communications. We capture this information through cookies, called a "beacon," that
we allow you to block.
Email Services
By entering in your email address on our website, you are subscribing (opting-in) to promotional email campaigns, which may include but not limited to special discounts, related products based on your order history, as well as helpful tips and installation advice regarding the items you have purchased. We use a third party platform to send promotional e-mails to customers as well as newsletter subscribers. Images contained in the email may be served by the third party. They may collect certain information about you such as your IP address, browser type, your operating system, the country and server your computer is logged onto, where the servers that your computer is logged onto is located, the time and date that a particular email was viewed, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad or email, products viewed and whether you continued on to make a purchase. If you do not wish to receive our promotional emails, you can easily unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of every email. For EU visitors, we will explicitly ask permission to send you marketing communications before doing so.
Other uses of personal data
We participate in remarketing advertising campaigns with third party vendors to display content specific advertisements to visitors that have previously visited motorcycleledlights.com. LEDGlow Lighting, LLC sponsored advertisements will be visible to visitors when those visitors go to other sites that participate in display network advertising. Third party vendors use first party, as well as third party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on a visitor’s past visits to motorcycleledlights.com's website. When creating & deploying remarketing advertising campaigns, we are fully compliant with policies on remarketing as required by our third party services. We do not use and/or run ads that collect any sensitive information about visitors including, but not limited to, email addresses, telephone numbers, and credit card numbers. Visitors can find more information how to opt out of personalized ads by visiting the links below.
NAI Consumer Opt Out
Criteo
Facebook
Twitter
How do we process your information?
We use an external provider to run our store, BigCommerce. BigCommerce is based in the US and is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and committed to providing best-in-class
service and data protection. You can check its participation in the Privacy Shield here on the official site of the International Trade Administration (ITA), U.S. Department of Commerce.
Through BigCommerce, we also use other, highly specialized external providers to provide the
most competitive services. For example:
Google
Microsoft
Bronto By Oracle
Facebook
Twitter
JustUno
Agile Harbor
The companies above may also use third party services of their own to optimally manage their platforms.
We may also from time to time evaluate other third party services designed to further improve your experience.
Our store is PCI-DSS compliant (a very strict industry standard with requirements for the security of credit card information), but we use accredited companies to process your credit card information such as Authorize.net & PayPal.
We integrate with a number of shipping companies to fulfill your orders which is provided to us by ShipStation.
Partnering with highly specialized external companies allows us to focus on what we do best:
selling great products.
How can you control your personal data?
If you are one of our customers who is in the EU, and we are specifically selling our products to the
Member State where you are located, you have specific rights that we are honored to enforce
without undue delay: Access, Correct, Erasure, Port, Object. If you cannot exercise your choice on
your account page or if you do not have an account with us, please reach out to us, at the contact
details at the bottom of this page. We will be more than happy to help. You can also review additional information here if you reside in the EU.
How long do we keep your data?
We keep your data for as long as you have an account with us. Most importantly, we have specific obligations for fraud detection and tax reasons as required by law. Therefore, we might need to retain certain data even if you ask to delete it.
Do we have any legal obligations when handling your data?
Many. Occasionally we may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without prior notice to you. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful.
Contacting LEDGlow Lighting, LLC. about privacy questions or concerns
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a message to:
Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer
LEDGlow Lighting, LLC.
444 Commerce Lane Suite B
West Berlin, NJ 08091
CustomerService@LEDGlow.com
Updates
If we update our Privacy Policy to reflect a change or improvement of our services or a new legal
obligation, we will publish the new version here on this specific page of our website.
×
OK
Get Special Offers
Email Address:
Thank you for signing up!
Copyright © 2020 Motorcycle LED Lights by LEDGlow. All Rights Reserved.
ILLUMINATE YOUR INBOX!
×
